21usdeal.com 2019-01-18

# Privacy Policy 21usDeal.com

**Privacy policy statement**

This web site is owned and operated by 21usDeal.com (21usDeal or we). 21usDeal takes user privacy seriously and makes reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to share with you our information collection and use practices. Please read this policy carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information described below. This policy applies solely to the web site and service located at www.21usDeal.com (the Service).

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted:

through our [Online Support System](https://www.21usdeal.com/contact-us/)

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
In order to use certain portions of the Service, you may be asked for, or you may choose to provide, certain personally identifiable information (PII) such as name, email address, postal address, PayPal account and similar information. We will not collect PII from you while you use the Service unless you voluntarily provide it to us or authorize us to collection such information.

You authorize 21usDeal to receive any account information from any affiliated merchant including, but not limited to, information regarding any purchase made by you through utilization of the Service, such as: the products ordered, the order number, the time and date of the purchase, the email address entered for the purchase.

**Collection on Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
21usDeal does collect and track certain non-personally identifiable (non-PII) information, including but not limited to, user IP numbers and browser type, access times, domain names, usage habits and other information which does not specifically identify any individual.

“Cookies” are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. We may use cookies to customize your use of the Service and for other purposes to improve your use of the Service, and may also use web beacons, web bugs, action tags and third party cookies. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. We do not use cookies to automatically retrieve PII from your computer without your knowledge.

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**  
21usDeal may use or disclose PII to operate and manage the Service, to provide services that you have requested or respond to your other inquires or requests. We may also disclose PII in the establishment or exercise of legal rights or defense against legal claims, to comply with applicable laws or regulations, to comply with a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order or to investigate suspected fraud or a violation of the terms of the 21usDeal User Agreement.

We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party not affiliated with 21usDeal without your consent, except in connection with the sale or merger of 21usDeal or the division responsible for such services.

You should be aware that PII which you voluntarily include and transmit online, such as in online forums, may be viewed and used by anyone with access to such forums. 21usDeal is unable to control such uses of your PII.

**Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We may use and disclose non-PII for any number of reasons, including but not limited to, working with business partners and improving our Service.

**Security**  
The security of your PII is very important to us and we take commercially reasonable steps to attempt to secure your PII. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. Only those employees and contractors who need access to your PII in order to perform their duties are authorized to have access. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and 21usDeal or information stored or transmitted through the Service or on our servers, will be completely free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers, and your use of the Service demonstrates your assumption of this risk.

**No Children under 13**  
We have no intention of collecting PII from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that PII from a child under 13 has been collected without such child’s parent or guardian’s consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. 21usDeal will post those changes on this page.

**User Agreement**  
Use of this Service is subject to the 21usDeal User Agreement located at[ https://www.21usdeal.com/terms-conditions/](https://www.21usdeal.com/terms-conditions/).

**United States**  
Our Service is maintained from within the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States, by using the Service, you authorize the export of PII to the United States and its storage and use as specified in this policy.

**Effective Date**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on November 10, 2011
